marinemax.com 2019-12-21

# Privacy Policy: MarineMax

At MarineMax, we are committed to protecting and preserving your privacy. MarineMax is the sole owner of any information collected via its website, mobile app, including, without limitation MarineMax Service Express, mailings, off-site events, or marketing activities. Any information collected by MarineMax will not be rented, sold, or traded to any outside sources. This Privacy Policy explains how information about you is collected, used and disclosed by MarineMax when you access or use our website, mobile app, sign up for emails, or otherwise interact with us. 

**Collection and Use of Information**  
MarineMax does want to communicate information that is interesting, newsworthy and relevant to you. We do this through our website, emails and mailings. The information we collect while you are on our website allows us to communicate information to you that is personalized to your interests.

As you use the MarineMax website we may collect information about you including the following:

**Log Information:** We collect information about your use of our website including the type of browser you use, access times, pages viewed, your IP address, and the page you visited before navigating to our website.

**Device Information:** We collect information about the computer or mobile device you use to access our website or mobile app, including hardware model, operating system and version, mobile network information and unique device identifiers. 

**Location Information:** We may collect information about your location when you access our website or mobile app.

**Information Collected by Cookies and Other Tracking Technologies:** MarineMax.com uses "cookies" which are small text files that are stored on the user's computer and gather and keep track of information related to the user. We may use cookies and other tracking technologies to collect information about you and your interactions with our website or mobile app including browsing behavior and engagement with our website or mobile app. This information is used to provide you with an experience on our website or mobile app that is relevant to your boating lifestyle and interests.  Although many website browsers are set to accept cookies, you can set your website browser to reject cookies, but this may prevent you from taking full advantage of our website features or receiving personalized information and services.

Information that you give us may be combined with other personally identifiable information (such as updated address and demographic information) from third-party sources to make our marketing efforts more efficient. Examples of other information we receive from third-party sources include updated delivery and address information, which we use to correct our records and deliver your next mailing more easily.

We use the information we collect for a variety of purposes, including to:

  * Personalize your experience with our website to be relevant to your boating lifestyle and interests
  * Communicate with you about news, events, MarineMax and partner offers, and other information we think will be of interest to you
  * Provide, maintain and improve the website
  * Monitor and analyze the website usage and trends
  * Process and deliver contest or sweepstakes entries and prizes

While on our website, you may choose to receive emails from MarineMax. Additionally while on our website, if you fill out a form requesting more information, you will be added to our email list. You may also sign up to receive our emails by contacting us at [marketing@marinemax.com](mailto:marketing@marinemax.com) or 727-531-1700. Upon signing up for MarineMax emails, you will receive the MarineMax monthly newsletter and emails about news, events, partner offers and other information we think will be of interest to you. As we learn more about you and your boating interest, we will strive to send you emails that are relevant to your boating lifestyle and interests.

**General Data Protection Regulation:** We value your privacy and are currently working on making our site better to ensure we meet the new data protection regulations in the European Union. Check back for more information.

**Sharing of Information**  
MarineMax is the sole owner of any information collected via its website, mobile app, mailings, off-site events, or marketing activities. Any information collected by MarineMax will not be rented, sold, or traded to any sources outside of MarineMax. MarineMax may share information with you from selected companies that we believe offer products or services of interest to you and are complimentary to your relationship with MarineMax. In doing this, we will not share your information with these companies; all such communications will originate from MarineMax.

**Your Choices**  
**Email:** You have the right to choose who you receive email from. MarineMax strives to make it easy for you to sign up to receive our emails as well as opt out of our emails.

You may choose to opt out from the emails we send to you through these methods:

  * In commercial emails that we send you, you may use the “unsubscribe” or “update your profile” included at the bottom of the email.
  * You may send an email to marketing@marinemax.com.
  * You may call 727-531-1700 and ask to speak to a team member in the marketing department.
  * You may send mail to the following address: Marketing, 2600 McCormick Drive, Suite 200, Clearwater, FL 33759.

After being added to our email list, you also may choose the types of emails you receive from us, including our monthly newsletter, emails with events, news and offers and emails from our online Boating Gear Center. Edits to your preferences can be made through these methods:

  * In commercial emails that we send you, you may use the “update your profile” included at the bottom of the email.
  * You may send an email to marketing@marinemax.com.
  * You may call 727-531-1700 and ask to speak to a team member in the marketing department.
  * You may send mail to the following address: Marketing, 2600 McCormick Drive, Suite 200, Clearwater, FL 33759.

**Postal Mail and Telephone:** If you would like to remove or edit your postal address or telephone number, please contact us through one of these methods: 

  * You may send an email to marketing@marinemax.com.
  * You may call 727-531-1700 and ask to speak to a team member in the marketing department.
  * You may send mail to the following address: Marketing, 2600 McCormick Drive, Suite 200, Clearwater, FL 33759.

**Cookies:** You can set your website browser to reject cookies, but this may prevent you from taking full advantage of our website features or receiving personalized services.

**Social Sharing Features**  
The website may offer social sharing features or other integrated tools, which let you share actions you take on the website with other media, and vice versa.  The use of such features enables the sharing of information with your friends or the public, depending on the settings you establish with the third party that provides the social sharing feature.  For more information about the purpose and scope of data collection and processing in connection with social sharing features, please visit the privacy policies of the third parties that provide these features.

Manage your cookie settings on this site.

 **California Privacy Rights**  
Under California law, California residents who have an established business relationship with MarineMax may opt out of MarineMax disclosing personal information about them to third parties for their marketing purposes. If you do not want MarineMax to disclose information to other companies for their marketing purposes, please contact Marketing at MarineMax via [marketing@marinemax.com](mailto:marketing@marinemax.com) or 727-531-1700.

**Contact Us**  
For additional information or to contact us regarding this website, MarineMax Inc. can be contacted at the following address:

MarineMax, Inc.  
2600 McCormick Dr.  
Suite 200  
Clearwater, FL 33759

Or via phone at (727) 531-1700

Or via e-mail at [marketing@marinemax.com](mailto:marketing@marinemax.com)

If any part of the MarineMax website links you to other websites or mobile applications, those websites and mobile applications do not operate under this privacy policy. We recommend that you examine the privacy statements posted on those other websites and mobile applications to understand their procedures for collecting, using, and disclosing personal information.

**Disclaimer:** MARINEMAX MAKES NO REPRESENTATIONS ABOUT THE SUITABILITY OF THE CONTENT OF ITS WEBSITE FOR ANY PURPOSE. ALL CONTENT IS PROVIDED "AS IS" WITHOUT ANY WARRANTY OF ANY KIND. ALL MANUFACTURERS HEREBY DISCLAIM ALL WARRANTIES AND CONDITIONS WITH REGARD TO THE PARTICULAR PURPOSE, TITLE AND NON-INFRINGEMENT. MARINEMAX DOES NOT WARRANT THE ACCESSIBILITY OF THE SITE OR THE AVAILABILITY OF ANY PRODUCTS DESCRIBED THEREIN. IN NO EVENT SHALL MARINEMAX BE LIABLE FOR ANY SPECIAL, INDIRECT, EXEMPLARY OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES OR ANY DAMAGES WHATSOEVER ARISING OUT OF OR IN CONNECTION WITH THE USE, COPYING OR DISPLAY OF THE CONTENT ON THIS SITE, INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, DAMAGES RELATING TO THE LOSS OF USE, DATA OR PROFITS, WITHOUT REGARD TO THE FORM OF ANY ACTION, INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED TO CONTRACT, NEGLIGENCE OR OTHER TORTIOUS ACTIONS. ALTHOUGH MARINEMAX HAS TRIED TO BE AS ACCURATE, COMPLETE AND CURRENT AS POSSIBLE, MARINEMAX DOES NOT WARRANT THAT THE CONTENT OF ITS WEBSITE OR MOBILE APP IS ACCURATE, COMPLETE OR CURRENT. THE CONTENT MAY INCLUDE TECHNICAL INACCURACIES OR TYPOGRAPHICAL ERRORS. IT IS YOUR RESPONSIBILITY TO VERIFY ANY INFORMATION BEFORE RELYING ON IT.

MarineMax reserves the right to change our Privacy Statement or the other notices contained herein. Any revisions will apply to data collected subsequent to the effective date of the change. Upon revising our privacy policy, we will update the Effective Date above.
